[Xinyun Kindergarten]
I am a child with zero sense of existence
Although young
But I seem to have known about this for a long time
So on the day of the kindergarten excursion
I insist not to wear a uniform, but a princess outfit
It seemed that I was going to the beach at that time.
Is it the East China Sea?
Or the West Sea
Still neither
Is it the South China Sea?
To be honest, I can't remember exactly
I just remember that everyone left in the end
I'm the only one left
To this day I still occasionally think about it
If I had listened to my mother at that time
If you wear your uniform obediently
Will he not be left there?
Even in the kindergarten, I still have no sense of presence.
No one cares about me
So I often miss my meal time
When I'm hungry in the middle of the night
I can only go to the faucet to drink water
but the strange thing is
No matter how much water you drink
My stomach is still empty
It's like water keeps flowing out from somewhere
Our way of going to and from school is quite special
[Sunshine Kindergarten]
Everyone will take the shuttle bus to the kindergarten together
If there is no kindergarten logo on the car,
Maybe you can even pretend to be an idol trainee
live in dormitory
[Seulgi is an orphan, it smells so disgusting]
Although no one will believe it
I have always had no sense of existence
To think you would be noticed for something like this
Really bad
do you know
People like us have unknown origins
It’s hard to even find a part-time job
So the seniors at the kindergarten
He kindly introduced us to the job
Going to the hospital to buy medicine
Use a forged ID card
[prescription note]
[pharmacy]
Are your grades good?
Where does it rank in the class?
Around 15th place
Not bad
There are only 30 people in a class now
Nothing to be proud of
Hey, what do you want to do in the future?
Don't know
I haven't thought about it
People must have dreams
So your dream is to exploit poor kids
Can you make a fortune selling medicine?
Give it to you
Those students in Gangnam, Seoul
I can’t even buy this if I want to.
Study hard
Don't go my way
If it is a person with excellent grades
The adults in the Victory in Life group told me this
I probably won’t even listen.
But for some reason, I heard a gangster say this
On the contrary, it is particularly convincing
So I started reading seriously for the first time in my life
What's the result?
I originally only ranked 15th in the class
He actually got 15th place in the school
Just a ranking
But it made other people's attitude towards me change greatly.
When I find myself even if I don’t eat
Can also feel full when
I started to become greedy
I want to get first place
[2023 Gyeongsangbuk-do Mathematics Competition Gold Medal
Yu Seqi]
You stinky bitch, why don't you speak?
It’s not just the adults who have changed
After I become a top student
Those people who used to always give me trouble
Never dare to mess with me again
Anyway
I must remain number one in the school
Because I would rather die
Don't want to go back to the past
Hey, that's all
what
Forget it
drive
By the way, today is my last time here
I'm moving to Seoul
seoul
Which district in Seoul are you moving to?
Jiangnan
Why, you were adopted by a rich family?
I found my dad
2024 academic year held today
College Subject Aptitude Test
Rated as the most difficult in history
Although the chairman of the committee who proposed the topic stated
The difficulty of the test questions is the same as last year
However, the actual physical sensations of candidates are quite different.
Especially the math questions are more difficult than expected
May become a top candidate
The key to getting into medical school
Seulgi, Seoul called
Good
Relevant persons indicate the subjects selected by the candidates
May affect final score
Because the difficulty of each subject varies greatly
Korean Educational Curriculum Assessment Service
After accepting applications for objections to test questions and answers,
Results will be announced on the 8th of next month
Next, I will give you the latest news
2024 University Entrance Examination Question Setting Committee
Shocking death
The following is an exclusive report by reporter Kim Jae-wook
["Good-natured Competition"]
thank you
[Surrounding Map]
[Discontinued during security check]
[Caihua Girls' High School]
[Southern Loop Road]
Call me when you have to go to class in the afternoon
I'll pick you up
Yeah
Take another look
Hello Cui Jing
wait for me
Who was that person just now?
Xiaojing, you always pretend that you are not interested in me
In the end, you still pay attention to me.
Met at the concert last week
I guess you guys will break up soon
Yeah, I just dumped him.
But he doesn't seem to have noticed yet
Buddha saves the poor sentient beings
Namo Amitabha
can i ask you a question
why are you walking so fast
Already a senior year of high school
Instead of wasting time waiting for traffic lights and traffic jams
It's better to walk faster
It's exactly what I thought
at this speed
It takes exactly 20 minutes to get to the classroom from home
Hello Cui Jing
Wait for me
Hello teacher
who are you
I'm the new transfer student here today
Where do your grades fall roughly?
[Korea University Ranking]
I transferred to another school in my senior year of high school and my parents didn’t come.
Leave students alone?
You go to the classroom of Class 2 first
And…
Yes
Can you come tomorrow wearing the correct uniform?
OK
Sorry, where is the classroom for the third year of high school?
[Caihua Girls' High School Entrance Ceremony]
Classmate, please buy me a bouquet of flowers.
Sorry
Buy me a bouquet of flowers
The entrance ceremony is about to begin
What are you doing? Get this hawker out quickly.
ok mother in law
You can't sell flowers here. Come out now.
I won't go out
I can't go out until it's sold out
Mother-in-law, please get up quickly
you can't do this
I won't go out
I'll buy it
mother-in-law
I buy all the flowers from you
How much is the total
One flower costs 10,000 won
(Note: Approximately NT$216)
to you
Okay
- Come on, get up
-thank you
I'll take you out
Hello all freshmen
Welcome to Caihua Girls' High School
I am student representative Liu Jieyi
This school is Korea’s top private school
117 years of rich history and tradition
Be my school girl
It’s also something you can be proud of
right
I'm kidding
Dear freshmen and guests
Please sit upright
before the entrance ceremony begins
We need to observe a minute's silence first
Teacher Yu Daohe who has taught in our school for four years
Unfortunately passed away recently
we will always remember
As an excellent teacher, he
and the spirit of an honest educator
What he cares most about is the learning atmosphere on campus
We shouldn't be affected by this
So we will follow the wishes of the bereaved
Conduct a brief memorial service
All…
Silence
Okay then...
Caihua Girls’ High School for the 2024 academic year
The entrance ceremony officially begins
If you are not a student of this school, please leave immediately
[2024 Caihua Girls’ High School Admissions Briefing]
Let's get started
After introducing the history of the school
Let’s take a look at our campus environment
This is Caihua’s pride, the open-air theater
There are more than 40 different clubs in our school
There are even medical societies
In this building
Through healthy competition with their peers, Caihua students
Create academic excellence
This is because we have exceeded 28% every year
This is evident in the medical school acceptance rate
In addition, Caihua’s students
In major domestic and foreign competitions
And continue to create brilliant records
please be proud of yourself
Sincerely looking forward to the new students
In the future, we can create new heights for Caihua
thank you all
[Class 2, Grade 3]
Scholarships will be awarded next
Han Zhenyuan
Where have you been? Just come in now
Find a seat quickly and sit down
March 4, 2024
Please invite Liu Taijun, president of the Parents’ Association, to come on stage to present the award.
congratulations
Next Kim Yeon Soo
Kim Yeon-soo will receive a scholarship certificate
Scholarship with 3 million won
(Note: Approximately NT$64,000)
congratulations
[Caihua Girls' Senior High School
Scholarship 3 million won]
Please give them a warm round of applause
No. 7 is the first interview strategy class
Submission of admission consultation form
Your preferred university and department should be filled in to your third choice
Prerequisite courses will be announced on the 10th
impact assessment report
There will be the first mock test on the 28th
Everyone must submit a study plan for this semester
Goal achievement setting…
How many of you can pass the exam?
What about Korea University School of Medicine?
Any other questions?
Teacher, which class is Liu Jieyi in?
Why do you ask this?
Of course we want to know
I also want to know
Tell us
Liu Jieyi, the teacher has high expectations for you
you know
I will work hard
There are only 255 days left until the university entrance exam
Okay, the class meeting is over
Give me my stuff back
Jay
this is your seat
I kept it specially for you
nice to meet you
My name is...
I know your name is Liu Jieyi
i just heard
Thanks to Jai Daddy for your annual donation of equipment
let medical society
Became Caihua’s pride
Still remember when this club was first established?
Teacher Yu is really working hard
Should we hold a memorial service for him?
what a shame
After all, he serves as a committee member for the university entrance exam
It's a first-class secret and must be kept secret from family members.
We also received instructions from our superiors
That’s why the school teachers and students were not allowed to attend his funeral.
Don't blame yourself too much
[Donation to J Medical Center Liu Taijun]
Would you like to have a cup of tea in my office?
good
Hello transfer student
Why don't you switch seats with me?
No, switch with me
Switch with me, please
You people are so shameless
How can you ask for it for nothing?
The seat next to Jay
transfer student
Ignore them and switch with me
As long as you are willing to trade with me
I'll buy you whatever you want
No price limit
How is it
Jin Nali, you want to settle everything with money again?
This is too unfair, right?
Let's play fair. Let's play guessing games.
If you don't win, you lose. Rock-paper-scissors.
cloth…
I don't lack anything
Nali
Where are you sitting now?
Me?
I sit in the middle of the classroom, in the second row
Right in front of the lectern, I can hear it clearly
The content of the teacher’s lecture
You can also see the blackboard clearly. The field of view is super good.
ok
Then I'll trade with you
Yeah awesome
What?
Transfer student, are you good at studying?
so disappointing
Then I can go
Tell me what you want
Don't regret it when the time comes
It seems you are really rich
Then can you give me a building?
what
Forget it, you don't have to spend money on me
Buy your own cosmetics
I've been looking for you for a long time
Let's go to dinner together
Let's go
I'm so hungry